T. J. Anderson Papers MS006
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Compositions by T.J. Anderson, 1956 -- 2004; 1975 -- 2004; MS006.003; 18.25 Linear Feet
  - Bahia, brasil, 1990; MS006.003.012.00009 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 9)
    Handwritten manuscript(score); chamber orchestra.
  - Americas millenium tribute to Adolphe Sax volume 5, 2001; MS006.003.012.00010 (Box 12)
    CD
  - Beyond silence, 1973; MS006.003.012.00011 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 9)
    Handwritten manuscript(score); text: pauline handson; tenor, clarinet, trombone, ciola, cello, piano.
  - Block songs, 1972; MS006.003.012.00012 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 9)
    Handwritten manuscript, text: Pearl Lomax; solo soprano, children's toys, chormatic pitch pipe, jack-in-the-box; associated material can be found at MS006/003-032#00002.
  - Boogie woogie concertante, 2003; MS006.003.012.00013 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 9)
    Handwritten manuscript(score); improvised solo piano, wind insturments, percussion.
  - Boogie woogie fantasy, 1997; MS006.003.012.00014 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 9)
    Handwritten manuscript(score), piano.
  - Bridging and branching, 1986; MS006.003.012.00015 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 9)
    Handwritten manuscript(score); flute, double bass.
  - Broke baroque, 1996; MS006.003.012.00016 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 9)
    Handwritten manuscript; violin, piano.
  - Call and response, 1982; MS006.003.012.00017 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 9)
    Handwritten manuscript; piano.
  - Castle house rag, 1975; MS006.003.012.00018 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 9)
    Handwritten manuscript(viola), copy(viola); viola; music: James Reese Europe, arrangement: T.J. Anderson; associated material can be found at MS006/003-032#00003.
  - Chamber concerto (Remembrances), 1988; MS006.003.012.00019 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 9)
    Handwritten manuscript(score); chamber symphony.
  - The new Amerian scene II, 1998; MS006.003.012.00020 (Box 12)
  - Chamber symphony, 1969; MS006.003.013.00001 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 9)
  - Classical symphony, 1961; MS006.003.013.00002 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 9)
    Copy(score); orchestra.
  - Classical symphony, 1961; MS006.003.013.00003 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 9)
    Reverse image(score); orchestra.
  - Concerto for two violins and chamber orchestra, 1988; MS006.003.013.00004 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 9)
    Handwritten manuscript(score); violin, orchestra.
  - Connections: a fantasy for string quartet, 1966; MS006.003.013.00005 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 9)
    Handwritten manuscript(score), copy(score);string quintet.
  - Dear John, dear Coltrane, 1989; MS006.003.014.00001 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 7)
    handwritten manuscript(score), copy(score); text: Michael Harper; choir, piano; associated material can be found at MS006/003-032#00004.
  - Echoes, 1988; MS006.003.014.00002 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 7)
    Handwritten manuscript, copy(score); oboe, bassoon.
  - Egyptian diary, 1991; MS006.003.014.00003 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 7)
    Handwritten manuscript(score), copy(score); text: Pauline Kaldas; soprano and two percussionists; associated material can be found at MS006/003-032#00005.
  - Episode I, 1980; MS006.003.014.00004 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 7)
    This date is approximate; handwritten manuscript(score); text: John Masefield.
  - Eternal april, 1980; MS006.003.014.00005 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 7)
    handwritten manuscript(score)
  - Etude for strings, 1980; MS006.003.014.00006 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 7)
    This date is approximate; handwritten manuscript onion skins(violin, viola, cello, double bass) copy (violin, viola, cello, double bass); violin, viola, cello, double bass.
  - Fanfare, 1976; MS006.003.015.00001 (Box Small Map Case 1 Drawer 4)
    Commissioned by the American Wind Symphony Orchestra for the Bicentennial of the United States; handwritten manuscript(score); solo trumpet, 4 mini-bands.
  - Fanfare for school volunteers of boston, 1986; MS006.003.015.00002 (Box Small Map Case 1 Drawer 4)
    Copy(score); trumpet, horns, trombones, tuba, tenor drum.
  - First love: a song for Nadia, 1997; MS006.003.015.00003 (Box Small Map Case 1 Drawer 4)
    Printed(score); voice, combo.
  - Five etudes and a fancy, 1964; MS006.003.015.00004 (Box Small Map Case 1 Drawer 4)
    Copy(score); woodwind quintet.
  - Five etudes and a fancy, 1964; MS006.003.015.00005 (Box Small Map Case 1 Drawer 4)
    Handwritten manuscript(score), copy(flute, oboe, clarinet, horn bassoon); woodwind quintet.
  - Five portraitures of two people, 1965; MS006.003.015.00006 (Box Small Map Case 1 Drawer 4)
    Handwritten manuscript(score); SATB voices, orchestra.
  - Four spirituals, 1979; MS006.003.015.00007 (Box Small Map Case 1 Drawer 4)
    handwritten manuscript(score), handwritten onion skins(score), copy(score)
  - From earth come iron, 1986; MS006.003.016.00001 (Box Small Map Case 1 Drawer 4)
    Handwritten manuscript(score); orchestra, jazz quintet, contralto, baritone; Associated material can be found at MS006/003-032#00006.
  - From earth come iron, 1986; MS006.003.016.00002 (Box Small Map Case 1 Drawer 4)
    Handwritten onion skin (score); orchestra, jazz quintet, contralto, baritone; Associated material can be found at MS006/003-032#00006.
  - From earth come iron, 1986; MS006.003.016.00003 (Box Small Map Case 1 Drawer 4)
    Copy(score); orchestra, jazz quintet, contralto, baritone; Associated material can be found at MS006/003-032#00006.
  - From earth come iron, 1986; MS006.003.016.00004 (Box Small Map Case 1 Drawer 4)
    Handwritten manuscript; orchestra, jazz quintet, contralto, baritone; Associated material can be found at MS006/003-032#00006.
  - Game play, 2001; MS006.003.017.00001 (Box 17)
    Handwritten manuscript(score), copy(score); flute, viola, cello, harp.
  - Game play, 2001; MS006.003.017.00002 (Box 17)
    Copy(flute, viola, cello, harp); flute, viola, cello, harp.
  - Gospel ghost, 2003; MS006.003.017.00003 (Box 17)
    Handwritten manuscript(score), handwritten onion skins (score), copy(score); flute, piano.
  - Grace and beauty, 1975; MS006.003.017.00004 (Box 17)
    Handwritten manuscript(trumpet, clarinet), copy(trumpet, clarinet); music: James Scott, Arrangement: T. J. Anderson; clarinet, trumpet; associated material can be found at MS006/003-032#00003.
  - Grace for string quartet, 1994; MS006.003.017.00005 (Box 17)
    Handwritten manuscript(score), handwritten manuscript(violin, viola, cello); violin, viola, cello.
  - Happy birthday Jack Zarker, 1978; MS006.003.017.00006 (Box 17)
    Handwritten manuscript(score); piano, voice.
  - Horizon '76, 1975; MS006.003.018.00001 (Box 18)
    Handwritten manuscript(score); soprano, orchestra; associated material can be found at MS006/003-032#00007.
  - Horizon '76, 1975; MS006.003.018.00002 (Box 18)
  - Horizon '76, 1975; MS006.003.018.00003 (Box 18)
    Copy(score); soprano, orchestra; associated material can be found at MS006/003-032#00007.
  - Huh! (What did you say?), 1997; MS006.003.018.00004 (Box 18)
    Handwritten manuscript(score); solo violin, violin, viola, cello, solo clarinet; associated material can be found at MS006/003-032#00008.
  - Huh! (What did you say?), 1999; MS006.003.018.00005 (Box 18)
    CD; Associated material can be found at MS006/003-032#00008.
  - In memoriam: Graham Wooton, 1985; MS006.003.018.00006 (Box 18)
    Handwritten manuscript(score); organ.
  - In memoriam Malcolm X, 1974; MS006.003.019.00001 (Box 19)
    Copy(score); text: Robery Hayden: voice, orchestra.
  - In memoriam: Zach Walker, 1968; MS006.003.019.00002 (Box 19)
    Handwritten manuscript(score); band.
  - Inaugural piece, 1982; MS006.003.019.00003 (Box 19)
    Handwritten manuscript(score), trumpet, trombone.
  - Intermezzi, 1983; MS006.003.019.00004 (Box 19)
    Handwritten manuscript(score), handwritten manuscript(clarinet, alta sax, piano); b flat soprano clarinet, e flat also sax, piano.
  - Intervals, 1970 -- 1971; MS006.003.019.00005 (Box 19)
    Handwritten manuscript(score) I-VI; orchestra.
  - Videmus: works by T.J. Anderson, David Baker, Donal Fox, Olly Wilson, 1992; MS006.003.019.00006 (Box 19)
  - Intervals, 1970 -- 1971; MS006.003.019.00007 (Box 19)
    Handwritten manuscript(score) VII; orchestra.
  - Introduction and allegro for orchestra instrumentation, 1959; MS006.003.019.00008 (Box 19)
    Handwritten manuscript(score); orchestra.
  - Invesiana, 1988; MS006.003.019.00009 (Box 19)
    Handwritten manuscript(score); violin, piano, cello.
  - Jazz influence in the music of T.J. Anderson, 1997; MS006.003.019.00010 (Box 19)
    Handwritten onion skins, copy; associated material can be found at MS006/003-032#00009.
  - Jonestown, 1982; MS006.003.019.00011 (Box 19)
    Handwritten manuscript(score); children's choir, piano.
  - Junk man rag, 1975; MS006.003.019.00012 (Box 19)
    Handwritten manuscript(coronet, clarinet), copy; music: C. Luckyth Roberts, Arrangement: T.J. Anderson; coronet, clarinet; associated material can be found at MS006/003-032#00003.
  - Lines and 6 etudes for string quartet, 1980; MS006.003.020.00001 (Box Small Map Case 1 Drawer 4)
    This date is approximate; handwritten manuscript; string quartet.
  - Loneliness, 1980; MS006.003.020.00002 (Box Small Map Case 1 Drawer 4)
    This date is approximate; handwritten manuscript(score).
  - Messages: a creole fantasy, 1979; MS006.003.020.00003 (Box Small Map Case 1 Drawer 4)
    Handwritten manuscript(score); orchestra; associated material can be found at MS006/003-032#00010.
  - A musical kaddish in Sea for John Zimarowski, 1995; MS006.003.020.00004 (Box Small Map Case 1 Drawer 4)
    Handwritten manuscript(score); text: Mark L. Bellletini; soprano, piano; associated material can be found at MS006/003-032#00011.
  - New dances, 1960; MS006.003.020.00005 (Box Small Map Case 1 Drawer 4)
    Handwritten manuscript(score); orchrstra.
  - Notes from a friend, 2000; MS006.003.020.00006 (Box Small Map Case 1 Drawer 4)
    Handwritten manuscript(score), copy(score); b flat clarinet, viola, cello.
  - Ode for Georga Russell on his 75th birthday, 1998; MS006.003.021.00001 (Box 21)
    Handwritten manuscript(score).
  - Passacaglia and blues, 1990; MS006.003.021.00002 (Box 21)
    Handwritten manuscript(score); piano.
  - Personals, 1966; MS006.003.021.00003 (Box 21)
    Copy(score); text: Arna Bontemps; chorus, brass ensemble, narrator; associated material can be found at MS006/003-032#00012.
  - Pine apple rag, 1975; MS006.003.021.00004 (Box 21)
    Handwritten manuscript(score), copy(score), printed copy, handwritten onion skins(violin, viola, cello, bass, flute, oboe, clarinet, bassoon, trumpet, horn, trombone, tuba, perscussion, piano ); text:Joe Snyder, music:Scott Jopline, arrangement: T. J. Anderson; orchestra, solo voice, chorus; associated material can be found at MS006/003-032#00003.
  - Play me something, 1979; MS006.003.021.00005 (Box 21)
    Handwritten manuscript(score); piano; associated material can be found at MS006/003-032#00013.
  - Pyknon overture, 1958; MS006.003.021.00006 (Box 21)
    Handwritten manuscript(score), handwritten manuscript(oboe, bassoon, bass drum, double bass, clarinet, cello, violin, trombone, trumpet, viola, horn, timpani, flute, piccolo); orchestra.
  - Ragtime oriole, 1975; MS006.003.021.00007 (Box 21)
    Handwritten manuscript(score), handwritten maunscript(viola, coronet, clarinet); music: James Scott, Arrangement: T. J. Anderson; viola, coronet, clarinet; associated material can be found at MS006/003-032#00003.
  - A real slow drag, 1975; MS006.003.021.00008 (Box 21)
    Copy (parts); Associated material can be found at MS006/003-032#00003.
  - Re-Creation, 1978; MS006.003.021.00009 (Box 21)
    Copy(score); text: Leon Forrest; readers, dancer, violin, cello, trumpet, alta sax, piano, drums; associated material can be found at MS006/003-032#00014.
  - Rotations, 1967; MS006.003.021.00010 (Box 21)
    Handwritten manuscript(score); woodwinds, crass, percussion.
  - Sensations, 1980; MS006.003.021.00011 (Box 21)
    Handwritten manuscript(clarinet, coronet), copy(clarinet, coronet); music: Joseph F. Lamb, arrangement: T.J. Anderson, clarinet, coronet.
  - The shell fairy, 1976 -- 1977; MS006.003.022.00001 (Box 22)
    Handwritten manuscript(score); atory: Chester S. Pierce, adaptation and lyrics: Sara S Beattie; soloists, chorus, dancers, piano or chamber orchestra; associated material can be found at MS006/003-032#00015.
  - Shouts (forty improvisatios for Eva-Maria), 1997; MS006.003.022.00002 (Box 22)
    Handwritten manuscript(score), handwritten manuscript(oboe, violin, cello, piano), handwritten onion skins(oboe, violin, cello, piano); oboe, violin, cello, piano.
  - Shouts (Forty Improvisatios for Eva-Maria), 1997; MS006.003.022.00003 (Box 22)
    Printed copy(oboe, cello); obow, violin, cello, piano.
  - Show piece, 1980; MS006.003.022.00004 (Box 22)
    This date is approximate; handwritten manuscript.
  - Sinfonia concertante for band, 1980; MS006.003.022.00005 (Box 22)
    This date is approximate; handwritten manuscript; band.
  - Slavery documents v2, 2002; MS006.003.022.00006 (Box 22)
    Handwritten manuscript(score); cantata singers, ensemble; associated material can be found at MS006/003-032#00016.
  - Soldier boy, soldier, 1982; MS006.003.023.00001 (Box 23)
    Handwritten manuscript(score); opera; associated material can be found at MS006/003-032#00017.
  - Soldier boy, soldier, 1982 -- 1985; MS006.003.023.00002 (Box 23)
    Copy(score); opera; associated material can be found at MS006/003-032#00017.
  - Soldier boy, soldier, 1982 -- 1985; MS006.003.023.00003 (Box 23)
    Libretto; associated material can be found at MS006/003-032#00017.
  - Sonata for unaccompanied violin, 1957; MS006.003.024.00001 (Box 24)
    Dissertation; handwritten manuscript onion skin(violin); violin.
  - Sonata for woodwind quintet and piano, 1956; MS006.003.024.00002 (Box 24)
    Handwritten manuscript (score), handwritten manuscript(oboe, flute, clarinet, bassoon, F horn); oboe, flute, clarinet, bassoon, f horn.
  - Sonata in D for piano and violin, 1957; MS006.003.024.00003 (Box 24)
    Handwritten manuscript onion skin(score), handwritten manuscript onion skin(viola, piano), copy(score), copy(viola, piano); piano, viola.
  - Sonata in D for piano and violin, 1957; MS006.003.024.00004 (Box 24)
    Copy (score), piano, viola.
  - A song for Elma Lewis, 2004; MS006.003.024.00005 (Box 24)
    Printed(score), handwritten manuscript(score), handwritten onion skins(score), copies(score); text: T. J. Anderson III, soprano, piano; associated material can be found at MS006/003-032#00026.
  - Songs of illumination, 1990; MS006.003.024.00006 (Box 24)
    Copy(score); soprano, tenot, piano.
  - Songs of illumination, 1998; MS006.003.024.00007 (Box 24)
  - Spirit songs, 1993; MS006.003.024.00008 (Box 24)
    Handwritten manuscript(score), handwritten onion skins(score, piano, cello); piano, cello.
  - Spirituals, 1979; MS006.003.024.00009 (Box 24)
    Handwritten manuscript(score); text: Robert Hayden; orchestra, jazz quartet, chorus, children's choir, tenor, narrator.
  - Squares (an essay for orchestra), 1965; MS006.003.024.00010 (Box 24)
    Handwritten manuscripts, orchestra.
  - Street song, 1977; MS006.003.024.00011 (Box 24)
    Handwritten manuscript(score), copy(score), onion skins; piano.
  - String quartet no. 1, 1958; MS006.003.025.00001 (Box 24)
    Handwritten manuscriupt(score); violin, viola, cello.
  - The suit, 1998; MS006.003.025.00002 (Box 25)
    Printed (score); text: Phillip Levine; male choir; associated material can be found at MS006/003-032#00027.
  - Sunstar, 1994; MS006.003.025.00003 (Box 25)
    Handwritten manuscript, copy; trumpet, cassette recorder.
  - Swing set, 1972; MS006.003.025.00004 (Box 25)
    Handwritten manuscript(score); clarinet, piano.
  - Symphony in three movements, 1964; MS006.003.025.00005 (Box 25)
  - This house, 1971; MS006.003.025.00006 (Box 25)
    Handwritten manuscript(score); text: T. J. Anderson; male glee club; chromatic pitch pipes.
  - Thomas Jefferson's minstrels, 1982; MS006.003.025.00007 (Box 25)
    Handwritten manuscript(score), handwritten onion skin(score); text: T. J. Anderson; baritone, male glee club, jazz band; associated material can be found at MS006/003-032#00028.
  - Thomas Jefferson's minstrels, 1982; MS006.003.025.00008 (Box 25)
    Copy (score), handwritten onion skin(score); text: T. J. Anderson; baritone, male glee club, jazz band; associated material can be found at MS006/003-032#00028.
  - Thomas Jefferson's orbiting minstrels and contraband, 1986; MS006.003.026.00001 (Box 26)
    Manuscript (score); string quartet, woodwind quintet, jazz sextet, dancer, soprano.
  - Music in Europe and the United States disc 1, 1990; MS006.003.026.00002 (Box 26)
  - Music in Europe and the United States disc 2, 1990; MS006.003.026.00003 (Box 26)
  - Music in Europe and the United States disc 3, 1990; MS006.003.026.00004 (Box 26)
  - Music in Europe and the United States disc 4, 1990; MS006.003.026.00005 (Box 26)
  - Together and alone, 1980; MS006.003.026.00006 (Box 26)
    This date is approximate; handwritten manuscript (trumpet, horn, trombone, tuba); brass quartet.
  - Tone poem of a steel mill, 1980; MS006.003.026.00007 (Box 26)
    This date is approximate; handwritten manuscript(score); orchestra.
  - Transitions: a fantasy for 10 insturments, 1971; MS006.003.026.00008 (Box 26)
    Handwritten manuscript (score); chamber ensemble.
  - Treemonisha, 1982; MS006.003.027.00001 (Box 27)
    Copy(score); orchestra; associated material can be found at MS006/003-032#00031.
  - Treemonisha, 1982; MS006.003.027.00002 (Box 27)
    Reverse image; orchrstra; associated material can be found at MS006/003-032#00031.
  - Treemonisha, 1982; MS006.003.027.00003 (Box 27)
  - Treemonisha, 1982; MS006.003.027.00004 (Box 27)
  - Treemonisha, 1982; MS006.003.027.00005 (Box 27)
  - Treemonisha, 1982; MS006.003.028.00001 (Box 28)
  - Treemonisha, 1982; MS006.003.028.00002 (Box 28)
  - Trio concertante, 1960; MS006.003.029.00001 (Box 29)
    Handwritten manuscript (score); clarinet, trumpet, trombone, chamber wind ensemble.
  - Trio sonata in E, 1956; MS006.003.029.00002 (Box 29)
    Dissertation; handwritten manuscript (score), handwritten manuscript(trombone, trumpet); trumpet, trombone.
  - Unit for orchestra piece, 1975; MS006.003.029.00003 (Box 29)
  - Untitled, 1956; MS006.003.029.00004 (Box 29)
    Handwritten manuscript
  - Variations on a chorale tune, 1957; MS006.003.029.00005 (Box 29)
    Handwritten onion skins, copy; organ.
  - Variations on a theme by Alban Berg, 1977; MS006.003.029.00006 (Box 29)
    Handwritten manuscript(score); viola, piano.
  - Variations on a theme by M.B. Tolson, 1969; MS006.003.029.00007 (Box 29)
    Handwritten manuscript(score); soprano, violin, cello, alto sax.
  - Vocalise, 1980; MS006.003.029.00008 (Box 29)
    Handwritten manuscript(score); violin, harp.
  - Walker, 1992; MS006.003.030.00001 (Box 30)
    Copy(score); chamber opera, text: Derek Walcott; associated material can be found at MS006/003-032#00041.
  - Walker, 1992; MS006.003.030.00002 (Box 30)
  - Walker, 1992; MS006.003.030.00003 (Box 30)
  - Walker, 1992; MS006.003.030.00004 (Box 30)
  - Walker, 1992; MS006.003.030.00005 (Box 30)
  - Walker, 1992; MS006.003.031.00001 (Box 31)
    Handwritten manuscript (score); chamber opera, text: Derek Walcott; associated material can be found at MS006/003-032#00041.
  - Watermelon revisited, 2001; MS006.003.031.00002 (Box 31)
  - Watermelon revisited, 1999; MS006.003.031.00003 (Box 31)
  - What ever happened to the big bands?, 1991; MS006.003.031.00004 (Box 31)
    Handwritten manuscript(alto sax, trumpet, trombone); alto sax trumpet, trombone.
  - What time is it?, 1986; MS006.003.031.00005 (Box 31)
    Handwritten manuscript(score); text: T. J. Anderson; choir, jazz orchestra; associated material can be found at MS006/003-032#00045.
  - Words my mother taught me, 2000; MS006.003.031.00006 (Box 31)
    Handwritten manuscript(score); soprano, piano; associated material can be found at MS006/003-032#00046.
  - 7 cabaret songs, 1994; MS006.003.032.00001 (Box 32)
    Lyrics with notes from T.J. Anderson. Associated material can be found at MS006/003-012#00004.
  - Block songs, 1972; MS006.003.032.00002 (Box 32)
    Lyrics with notes from T.J. Anderson. Associated material can be found at MS006/003-013#00012.
  - Classic rags and ragtime songs, 1975; MS006.003.032.00003 (Box 32)
    Photocopies with notes from T.J. Anderson. Associated material can be found at MS006/003-012#00008, MS006/003-017#00004, MS006/003-019#00012, MS006/003-021#00004, MS006/003-021#00007, and MS006/003-021#00008. A recording of this work exists in the Jester Hairston collection (MS040) inscribed from T.J. Anderson to Jester Hairston, the recording can be found at MS040/001-003#00012.
  - Dear John, dear Coltrane, 1989; MS006.003.032.00004 (Box 32)
    Lyrics with notes from T.J. Anderson. Associated material can be found at MS006/003-014#00001
  - Egyptian diary, 1991; MS006.003.032.00005 (Box 32)
    Lyrics with notes from T.J. Anderson. Associated materical can be found at MS006/003-014#00003
  - From earth come iron, 1986; MS006.003.032.00006 (Box 32)
    Copyright information, notes from T. J. Anderson, articles, correspondence. Associated material can be found at MS006/003-016#00001.
  - Horizon '76, 1975; MS006.003.032.00007 (Box 32)
    Lyrics, notes from T. J. Anderson, correspondence, and copyright information. Associated material can be found at MS006/003-018#00001.
  - Huh! What did you say?, 1997; MS006.003.032.00008 (Box 32)
    Notes from T. J. Anderson. Associated material can be found at MS006/003-018#00004
  - Jazz influence in the music of T.J. Anderson, 1997; MS006.003.032.00009 (Box 32)
    Text with notes. Associated material can be found at MS006/003-019#00001.
  - Messages: a creole fantasy, 1979; MS006.003.032.00010 (Box 32)
    Source material. Associated material can be found at MS006/003-020#00003
  - A musical kaddish "in sea" for John Zimarowski, 1995; MS006.003.032.00011 (Box 32)
    Lyrics with notes from T. J. Anderson. Associated material can be found at MS006/003-020#00004.
  - Personals, 1966; MS006.003.032.00012 (Box 32)
    Program. Associated material can be found at MS006/003-021#00003.
  - Play me something, 1979; MS006.003.032.00013 (Box 32)
    Text with notes from T. J. Anderson. Associated material can be found at MS006/003-021#00005.
  - The shell fairy, 1978; MS006.003.032.00014 (Box 32)
    Text. Associated material can be found at MS006/003-021#00008.
  - The shell fairy, 1976 -- 1977; MS006.003.032.00015 (Box 32)
    Text. Associated material can be found at MS006/003-022#00001.
  - Slavery documents, 2002; MS006.003.032.00016 (Box 32)
    Program. Associated material can be found at MS006/003-022#00006.
  - Soldier boy, soldier, 1982; MS006.003.032.00017 (Box 32)
    Libretto. Associated material can be found at MS006/003-023#00001.
  - Soldier boy, soldier, 1982; MS006.003.032.00018 (Box 32)
    Libretto. Associated material can be found at MS006/003-023#0001.
  - Soldier boy, soldier, 1982; MS006.003.032.00019 (Box 32)
  - Soldier boy, soldier, 1982; MS006.003.032.00020 (Box 32)
  - Soldier boy, soldier, 1982; MS006.003.032.00021 (Box 32)
    Correspondence, articles, and programs. Associated material can be found at MS006/003-023#00001.
  - Soldier boy, soldier, 1982; MS006.003.032.00022 (Box 32)
    Programs, articles, correspondence, and the libretto. Associated material can be found at MS006/003-023#00001.
  - Soldier boy, soldier, 1982; MS006.003.032.00023 (Box 32)
    Programs, articles, correspondence, the libretto. Associated materical can be found at MS006/003-023#00001.
  - Soldier boy, soldier, 1982; MS006.003.032.00024 (Box 32)